also I'm looking at you the guy behind
us looking at me he's like I didn't know
Robin Williams and Jerry Springer had a
boy
[Applause]
just doesn't make no sense
also why I've got a Southern accent
right now don't make no sense
you don't know what I got I was working
in England and I was telling him this
and they're like hey it's okay you still
look like Freddy Krueger
the last show I did five people told me
ugly people they think I look like is
that
me you look a little like that Crypt
Keeper
terrible what
[Applause]
how did you get drunk in the dry bar man
do not
but pick someone I look anything I like
Tom Cruise and by the way I'm not asking
you to yell out people I look like right
now if that's okay
I kind of like the ugly
I know
that is so mean to her
I don't mind
I was oh my gosh I was in Vegas and this
woman I was doing this thing last June
my age had set up and this
he goes you know who you look like
you look like that Brad Pitt I was like
what she goes in the first 30 minutes of
Benjamin Button
is that me that's me
but thank you for trying to be nice
that's very nice even though you're way
off but you just had to pick somebody
good looking and think I'd stick
I was I was at Walmart Okay this is
weird not that I was at Walmart although
I I'm a little sketchy about going to
Walmart but anyway it's okay Walmart
it's weird how you go to Walmart
sometimes you see people like you see
stretch pants and tube tops and that's
men so anyway but uh
but the important thing is this was
Walmart I'm walking with a cart at
Walmart and a guy runs up he goes hey oh
my gosh you're Bill Gates look what I
said in Walmart
Bill Gates
that's the only joke I have there in
Walmart
Bill Gates we are not a bright people
that you have to understand would we
agree don't put the camera on anybody
would we agree that half the United
States yeah
yeah
I mean look I'm looking out of you and a
lot of you don't look that bright I'm
not gonna lie to you
and if you're mad at me right now you
just picked your team
but we'll do this in America we will
drive to the McDonald's and some kid 19
don't leave the pickle off the hamburger
we'll scream at them like they murdered
our families if we had a stick we would
beat people to death over cheese and our
kids are right there get him down
calm down
your life ain't that bad if this is your
problem
and let me give you a very useful tip
you drive to the McDonald's and think
your order is going to be right you're
the idiot
I know
if someone works at McDonald's and gets
10 orders right in a row they become
district manager
laughs everything